Last week I had told in the video that for just
two rupees you
can take accidental insurance for one area, 480 means you can take
20 lakh accidental insurance on a monthly basis for 40 rupees.
Today in this video I am going to
tell you that for just two hundred nineteen hundred
300 rupees, it will cost 1000 rupees.
You can take hospital cash benefit insurance. Yes,
now hospital cash insurance or
hospital admission, see if you fall
ill and get admitted in the hospital by mistake,
two, three or four times, then you have health
insurance, through this you can get whatever appointment
you get, but if you do a job
or you subscribe, which is
due to this or no one can understand them, due to which
some village or the other, apart from this,
this is nothing
and this is what happens in most of the eighty percent of India,
for the unorganized sector,
more than ever, if you are the
only earning member in the family and if you
take leave for four days and get admitted, then your
money will be deducted, that will be a loss and
who will pay for four days, in the same condition,
insurance companies have introduced a new benefit
in debit  Its name is Hospital Tyohar, it means
if you are admitted in the hospital on the
appointed day in 2009, the insurance company Aircel
number will give you ₹500 or thousands of rupees ₹2000
Delhi, yes subscribe Delhi,
most of the subscriptions keep coming till 2030
and if you are admitted in it then
instead of 500 you will have to pay thousands, instead of thousand rupees I will give ₹2000
Duggi and instead of ₹4000 I will give you ₹4000 day,
see here you should subscribe to this hospital,
for this it is necessary that when you
come to me you have a medical insurance subscription
or you don't have to do anything like that, just
subscribe for two days, please
this channel is not subscribed,
thank you, how to take it and how to see its policy terms
and conditions inside that,
first of all open it on your mobile phone, then
install it, here an
option comes below, click on it, as I will
click, then subscribe separately
and subscribe ₹2000 ₹4000 friends for ₹10
more  ₹500 people appointed hospital medical
hospital subscribe secondly during subscription like if
you took a system of 2,000 then you
get ₹4000 for thousands 2500 for thousands and you have
215 sterilization suppose you were
admitted for only 5 days in a year then
you will get ₹2000 per day for every day instead of four
days you will pay 10 and
in the remaining month of Saal Mubarak if you fill 10 days and
fill two days from three days then you will get
two days and you will get it again in children's dress that
means Meghna now by doing
method together or two, three or four days you will get 24
hospital hospital then
subscribe and subscribe to the channel
so you subscribe by clicking on details appointed here
you click on date of birth
village will automatically be Pandey
Pandey which you select here
and after that you can update from
any credit card debit card use wallet
like if you do it here then you will get the
policy document in 2 to 3 minutes
on your email id  And it will come on your email ID,
you can withdraw it or polyp,
then you can go to Koun or you can go to your phone and go to My
Money and go to the hospital,
as soon as you open it, then you will get the
details on the entire screen, policy certificate
number, this document cannot be taken from here also
and below there is an option 'Need More Help' in
which if you want to call then you have to click on the
toll free number till the bottom, then it is necessary to call on it
or email ID or the nearest
office on Monday, keep in mind to appoint
half the subscribers from your mobile
and their email ID and their date
is necessary and if you are subscribing then take a
printout of a copy of one document and keep it in your file,
if you already have health
insurance or life insurance, keep it with you
and tell all your family members that
I have taken this policy online and if I get
admitted then bring this also with me to the hospital
or definitely call on this toll free number
and anyway all
your documents like Aadhar card, PAN card, cheque, bank etc.,
market etc. certificates etc., policy,
life insurance, health insurance and or
bonds, commercial paper or
your personal related documents  It must be that I have
seen such people too, I say in every video that
I have seen such people who go to heaven,
if there is a God, but they have
these huge investments here and there,
but the people living in their first place do
not know their names, they make a microphone, but no one
knows that if the boy, your
husband, said to invest, then please
take all the confidential documents, keep them
in the file, keep them in the middle and the
mother and father of the first one are intelligent, tell them,
sorry Mandsaur, the children are small, so
tell them this on WhatsApp, if you liked the video
then please like, I wanted
Bhim to get the benefit of ₹1000 in
₹1200, hospital cash withdrawal, we are
getting interest of ₹2000 in ₹400, you can
also subscribe and if you have
any problem related to appointing the subscribe button, you
can comment below,
subscribe by sending a WhatsApp message.